David E. Lilienthal Papers, 1900-1981 (bulk 1950-1981 ): Inventory MC148
EADs for public policy collection from import batch
- Series 18: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1905 October 19-1981; 208 boxes; 2 items
  - Subseries 18E: 1962-1963, 14 boxes
    - Griswold, Erwin, 1963; 1 box (Box 438)
    - Gruening, Ernest, 1963; 1 box (Box 438)
    - Hafstad, L.R., 1963; 1 box (Box 438)
    - Haley, W.J., 1963; 1 box (Box 438)
    - Hamilton, Fowler, 1963; 1 box (Box 438)
    - Harvard Law Review, 1963; 1 box (Box 438)
    - Harvard Lam School, 1963; 1 box (Box 438)
    - Health, Education and Welfare Department, 1963; 1 box (Box 438)
    - Heffner, Richard D, 1963; 1 box (Box 438)
    - Hellman, Lillian, 1963; 1 box (Box 438)
    - Herald Tribune, 1963; 1 box (Box 438)
    - Hewlett, Richard G, 1963; 1 box (Box 438)
    - Hochschild, Harold K, 1963; 1 box (Box 438)
    - Hoffman, Claire Giannini, 1963; 1 box (Box 438)
    - Hughes, Richard J, 1963; 1 box (Box 438)
    - Humphrey, Hubert H, 1963; 1 box (Box 438)
    - Hun School, 1963; 1 box (Box 438)
    - Hunt, Richard, 1963; 1 box (Box 438)
    - Illinois, University of, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - Indiana, Sons of, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - Indiana University - Indiana Authors' Day, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - Informacion Comercial Espanola, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - Institute of International Education, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - Institute for International order, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - Institute for Policy Studies, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - International Committee for Scientific, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - Management, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - International Executives Association, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - International Science and Technology, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - International Social Science Journal, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - Re Iran, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - Iran-America Society, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - Iran American Chamber of Commerce, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - Iran Foundation, Inc, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - Re Ivory Coast, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - Jackson, Barbara, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - Jackson, Henry M, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - Jefferson Society of the University of Virginia, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - Katz, Milton, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - Kazan, Elia, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - Kennedy, John F, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - Kirk, Mrs. Alan G, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - Kiwanis Club of Chattanooga, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - Klein, Anna, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - Knoedler, M. and Co, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - Kraft, James, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - Krug, Julius A, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - Lazard Freres & Co, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - League for Industrial Democracy, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - Library of Congress - Manuscript Division, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - Life (Magazine), 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - Lilienthal, David E., Jr, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - Lilienthal, Theodore, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - Lippmann, Walter, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - Little, Brown and Co, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - Lively, Robert A, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - Lleras, Alberto, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - Loeb, Robert F, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - Los Angeles Times, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - Luce, Clare Boothe, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - Luce, Henry R, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - Lynagh, Paula and Vincent, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - Lyons, Leonard, 1963; 1 box (Box 439)
    - McGraw-Hill Book Company, 1963; 1 box (Box 440)
    - McKelway, St. Clair, 1963; 1 box (Box 440)
    - McNeil, Marshall, 1963; 1 box (Box 440)
    - MacLeish, Archibald, 1963; 1 box (Box 440)
    - Mansfield, Mike, 1963; 1 box (Box 440)
    - Marcy, Carl, 1963; 1 box (Box 440)
    - Marton, Elisabeth, 1963; 1 box (Box 440)
    - Meeman, Edward J, 1963; 1 box (Box 440)
    - Re Mexico, 1963; 1 box (Box 440)
    - Meyer, Andre, 1963; 1 box (Box 440)
    - Meyner, Helen and Robert B, 1963; 1 box (Box 440)
    - Michigan State University, 1963; 1 box (Box 440)
    - Minerals & Chemicals Philipp Corporation, 1963; 1 box (Box 440)
    - Miscellaneous, 1963; 1 box (Box 440)
    - Moe, Henry A, 1963; 1 box (Box 440)
    - Monnet, Jean, 1963; 1 box (Box 440)
    - Morehouse, Edward W, 1963; 1 box (Box 440)
    - Re Morocco, 1963; 1 box (Box 440)
    - Mowrer, Edgar A, 1963; 1 box (Box 440)
    - Murname, George, 1963; 1 box (Box 440)
    - Murphy, Franklin D, 1963; 1 box (Box 440)
    - Murrow, Edward R, 1963; 1 box (Box 440)
    - Museum of Modern Art, 1963; 1 box (Box 440)
    - Nassau Club, 1963; 1 box (Box 440)
    - Re National Conference on International Economic and Social Development, 1963; 1 box (Box 440)
    - Re National Council on Industrial Growth and Conversion, 1963; 1 box (Box 440)
    - National Observer, 1963; 1 box (Box 440)
    - Neumann, Emanuel, 1963; 1 box (Box 440)
    - New Hampshire University, 1963; 1 box (Box 440)
    - New York Times, 1963; 1 box (Box 440)
    - Nicely, James Mount, 1963; 1 box (Box 440)
    - Norstad, Lauris, 1963; 1 box (Box 440)
    - North American Newspaper Alliance, 1963; 1 box (Box 440)
    - North Carolina State University, 1963; 1 box (Box 440)
    - Re Nuclear Disarmament, 1963; 1 box
      - Re Nuclear Power Plants, 1963; 1 box
        - California, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 440)
        - New York, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 440)
    - Oakes, John B, 1963; 1 box (Box 440)
    - Re Oriental Institute, University of Chicago, 1963; 1 box (Box 441)
    - Pahlavi, Mohammed Reza, Shah of Iran, 1963; 1 box (Box 441)
    - Peace Hostage Exchange Foundation, 1963; 1 box (Box 441)
    - Pearson, Drew, 1963; 1 box (Box 441)
    - Perkins, James A, 1963; 1 box (Box 441)
    - Planned Parenthood Federation of America, 1963; 1 box (Box 441)
    - Price, Melvin, 1963; 1 box (Box 441)
    - Re Princeton University: University Magazine, 1963; 1 box (Box 441)
    - Prud'homme, Hector, 1963; 1 box (Box 441)
    - Re Publication by David E. Lilienthal: Change, Hope, and the Bomb. Princeton University Press, 1963; 1 box (Box 441)
    - Ragland, Mrs. Tom (Martha), 1963; 1 box (Box 441)
    - Rand Corporation, 1963; 1 box (Box 441)
    - Randolph, Jennings, 1963; 1 box (Box 441)
    - Resources for the Future, Inc, 1963; 1 box (Box 441)
    - Reston, James B, 1963; 1 box (Box 441)
    - Robinson, William J, 1963; 1 box (Box 441)
    - Rockefeller Foundation, 1963; 1 box (Box 441)
    - Rockefeller, John D., III, 1963; 1 box (Box 441)
    - Re Rockefeller Public Service Awards, 1963; 1 box (Box 441)
    - Roosevelt, Eleanor - Memorial Foundation, 1963; 1 box (Box 441)
    - Rorty, James, 1963; 1 box (Box 441)
    - Rosenak, Bertha, 1963; 1 box (Box 441)
    - Re Rutgers University, 1963; 1 box (Box 441)
    - Salinger, Pierre, 1963; 1 box (Box 441)
    - Salisbury, Harrison E, 1963; 1 box (Box 441)
    - Sarnoff, David, 1963; 1 box (Box 441)
    - Schary, Dore, 1963; 1 box (Box 441)
    - Re Scientific American, 1963; 1 box (Box 441)
    - Steaborg, Glenn T, 1963; 1 box (Box 441)
    - Shelton, Barrett C, 1963; 1 box (Box 441)
    - Sherman, Henry, 1963; 1 box (Box 441)
    - Shriven Robert Sargent, Jr, 1963; 1 box (Box 441)
    - Society for Advancement of Management, 1963; 1 box (Box 441)
    - Society for international Development, 1963; 1 box (Box 441)
    - Sorensen, Theodore C, 1963; 1 box (Box 441)
    - Re Speeches by David E. Lilienthal, 1963; 1 box
      - Stafford Little Lectures, Princeton University, 1963; 1 box
        - I. "The Mythology of Nuclear Disarmament", 1963; 1 box (Box 442)
        - II. "Whatever Happened to the Peaceful Atom?", 1963; 1 box (Box 442)
        - III. "Change, Hope and the Bomb,", 1963; 1 box (Box 442)
    - Spivak, Lawrence E, 1963; 1 box (Box 442)
    - State Department: Agency for International Development (AID), 1963; 1 box (Box 442)
    - Stevenson, Adlai E, 1963; 1 box (Box 442)
    - Stokes, Mrs. Thomas, 1963; 1 box (Box 442)
    - Strauss, Lewis L, 1963; 1 box (Box 442)
    - Sullivan, Ed, 1963; 1 box (Box 442)
    - Sullivan, Frank, 1963; 1 box (Box 442)
    - Sulzberger, Mrs. Arthur H, 1963; 1 box (Box 442)
    - Swidler, Joseph C, 1963; 1 box (Box 442)
    - Syracuse University - Library, 1963; 1 box (Box 442)
    - Szanton, Victor L, 1963; 1 box (Box 442)
    - Szold, Edwin D, 1963; 1 box (Box 442)
    - Taylor, Maxwell D, 1963; 1 box (Box 442)
    - Re Tennessee VIlley Authority, 1963; 1 box (Box 442)
    - Tennessee University, 1963; 1 box (Box 442)
    - Time (Magazine), 1963; 1 box (Box 442)
    - Tobey, Mr. and Mrs. Barney, 1963; 1 box (Box 442)
    - Tobey, David M, 1963; 1 box (Box 442)
    - Tobey, Nancy, 1963; 1 box (Box 442)
    - Tobey, William, 1963; 1 box (Box 442)
    - Truman, Harry S, 1963; 1 box (Box 442)
    - Re Truman Harry S. - Library, 1963; 1 box (Box 442)
    - Twentieth Century Fund, 1963; 1 box (Box 442)
    - United Jewish Appeal, 1963; 1 box (Box 443)
    - United States Army - War College, 1963; 1 box (Box 443)
    - Van Mourick, Lawrence L, 1963; 1 box (Box 443)
    - Viner, Jacob, 1963; 1 box (Box 443)
    - Volpe, Joseph Jr, 1963; 1 box (Box 443)
    - Voorduin, William L, 1963; 1 box (Box 443)
    - Warren, Earl, 1963; 1 box (Box 443)
    - Warren, Shields, 1963; 1 box (Box 443)
    - Washington Foreign Law Society, 1963; 1 box (Box 443)
    - Weinberg, Alvin M, 1963; 1 box (Box 443)
    - Weiner, Joseph L, 1963; 1 box (Box 443)
    - Wellesley College, 1963; 1 box (Box 443)
    - White, E.B., 1963; 1 box (Box 443)
    - Re White, Paul Dudley, 1963; 1 box (Box 443)
    - Wiesner, Jerome B, 1963; 1 box (Box 443)
    - Wigner, Eugene P, 1963; 1 box (Box 443)
    - Wildlife Management Institute, 1963; 1 box (Box 443)
    - Willard, Charles H, 1963; 1 box (Box 443)
    - Wilson, Edmund, 1963; 1 box (Box 443)
    - Wolman, Abel, 1963; 1 box (Box 443)
    - Woman's National Democratic Club, 1963; 1 box (Box 443)
    - Yale Law Journal, 1963; 1 box (Box 443)
    - Yeshiva University, 1963; 1 box (Box 443)
    - Young Men's Christian Association of Princeton, 1963; 1 box (Box 443)
    - Zionist Organization of America, 1963; 1 box (Box 443)
  - Subseries 18F: 1964, 1953-1964; 7 boxes
    This subseries contains correspondence and related material for 1964.
    - Acheson, Dean, 1964; 1 box (Box 444)
    - Agricultural Policy Institute, 1964; 1 box (Box 444)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1964; 1 box (Box 444)
    - American Assembly, 1964; 1 box (Box 444)
    - American Association of University Women (Denver Branch), 1964; 1 box (Box 444)
    - American Booksellers Association, 1964; 1 box (Box 444)
    - American Cancer Society, 1964; 1 box (Box 444)
    - Re American Commercial Barge Line Company, 1964; 1 box (Box 444)
    - Re American Commercial Lines, Inc, 1964; 1 box (Box 444)
      Includes the resignation of David E. Lilienthal as Director of the American Commercial Lines, Inc.
    - American Committee for the Weizmann Institute of Science, 1964; 1 box (Box 444)
    - American Council of Learned Societies, 1964; 1 box (Box 444)
    - American Jewish Archives, 1964; 1 box (Box 444)
    - American Public Power Association, 1964; 1 box (Box 444)
    - American Scholar, 1964; 1 box (Box 444)
    - American Society for Public Administration, 1964; 1 box (Box 444)
    - Anderson, Leo L, 1964; 1 box (Box 444)
    - Ansari, Abdol Reza, 1964; 1 box (Box 444)
    - Armstrong, Hamilton F, 1964; 1 box (Box 444)
    - Association of Urban Universities, 1964; 1 box (Box 444)
    - Atchley, Dana W, 1964; 1 box (Box 444)
    - Atlantic Council, 1964; 1 box (Box 444)
    - Atlantic Monthly Press, 1964; 1 box (Box 444)
    - Re Atomic Energy, 1964; 1 box (Box 444)
    - Re Atomic Energy Commission, 1964; 1 box (Box 444)
    - Re Barge Lines, 1964; 1 box (Box 444)
    - Barnes, Joseph, 1964; 1 box (Box 444)
    - Baruch, Bernard M, 1964; 1 box (Box 444)
    - Baumgartner, Leona, 1964; 1 box (Box 444)
    - Berle, Adolf A, 1964; 1 box (Box 445)
    - Bingham, Jonathan B, 1964; 1 box (Box 445)
    - Boston University, 1964; 1 box (Box 445)
    - Bowles, Chester, 1964; 1 box (Box 445)
    - Brazilian National War College, 1964; 1 box (Box 445)
    - Bromberger, Nancy, 1964; 1 box (Box 445)
    - Brooks, John, 1964; 1 box (Box 445)
    - Bulletin of the Atomic Scientists, 1964; 1 box (Box 445)
    - Bunker, Ellsworth, 1964; 1 box (Box 445)
    - Bunting, Mary, 1964; 1 box (Box 445)
    - Burnett, John G, 1964; 1 box (Box 445)
    - Business Week, 1964; 1 box (Box 445)
    - California University, 1964; 1 box (Box 445)
    - California University, Los Angeles: Honorary Degree conferred upon David E. Lilienthal, June 11, 1964, 1 box (Box 445)
    - Canfield, Cass, 1964; 1 box (Box 445)
    - Carlton, Winslow, 1964; 1 box (Box 445)
    - Carnegie Institute of Technology, 1964; 1 box (Box 445)
    - Case Institute of Technology, 1964; 1 box (Box 445)
    - Centennial Review of Arts and Science, 1964; 1 box (Box 445)
    - Century Association, 1964; 1 box (Box 445)
    - Chase Manhattan Bank, 1964; 1 box (Box 445)
    - Chattanooga Times, 1964; 1 box (Box 445)
    - Chicago Daily News, 1964; 1 box (Box 445)
    - Re Clapp, Gordon R, 1964; 1 box (Box 445)
    - Clifford, Clark M, 1964; 1 box (Box 445)
    - Coates, Albert, 1964; 1 box (Box 445)
    - Coffin, Frank M, 1964; 1 box (Box 445)
    - Re Colombia, 1964; 1 box (Box 445)
    - Colorado State Chamber of Commerce, 1964; 1 box (Box 445)
    - Columbia Journal of World Business, 1964; 1 box (Box 445)
    - Committee for Economic Development, 1964; 1 box (Box 445)
    - Conference upon Research and Education in World Government (CURE), 1964; 1 box (Box 445)
    - Congress of Scientists on Survival, 1964; 1 box (Box 445)
    - Congressional Digest, 1964; 1 box (Box 445)
    - Conservation Foundation, 1964; 1 box (Box 445)
    - Re Contemporary Authors, Gale Research Company, 1964; 1 box (Box 445)
    - Coombs, Philip H, 1964; 1 box (Box 445)
    - Cooperative Forum, 1964; 1 box (Box 445)
    - Cornell, Katharine, 1964; 1 box (Box 445)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, 1964; 1 box (Box 445)
    - Cousins, Norman, 1964; 1 box (Box 445)
    - Cuccia, Enrico, 1964; 1 box (Box 445)
    - Daniels, Jonathan, 1964; 1 box (Box 446)
    - Delta Upsilon Fraternity, 1964; 1 box (Box 446)
    - Democratic Party, 1964; 1 box (Box 446)
    - Denver Post, 1964; 1 box (Box 446)
    - Denver Public Library, 1964; 1 box (Box 446)
    - DePauw University, 1964; 1 box (Box 446)
    - Development and Resources Corporation, 1964; 1 box (Box 446)
    - Dyson, Freeman J, 1964; 1 box (Box 446)
    - Eberstadt, Ferdinand, 1964; 1 box (Box 446)
    - Edson, Peter, 1964; 1 box (Box 446)
    - Education and World Affairs, Inc. (EWA), 1964; 1 box (Box 446)
    - Elliot, Karl, 1964; 1 box (Box 446)
    - Ernst, Morris L, 1964; 1 box (Box 446)
    - Farmanfarmaian, Khodadad, 1964; 1 box (Box 446)
    - Ferris, John P, 1964; 1 box (Box 446)
    - Finley, States Rights, 1964; 1 box (Box 446)
    - First Unitarian Church, Wilmington, Delaware, 1964; 1 box (Box 446)
    - Ford Foundation, 1964; 1 box (Box 446)
    - Foreign Policy Association, 1964; 1 box (Box 446)
    - Fortune (magazine), 1964; 1 box (Box 446)
    - Four Freedoms Foundation, 1964; 1 box (Box 446)
    - Fowler, Henry H, 1964; 1 box (Box 446)
    - Frankfurter, Felix, 1964; 1 box (Box 446)
    - Freedom House, 1964; 1 box (Box 446)
    - Friendly, Alfred, 1964; 1 box (Box 446)
    - Friendly, Fred W, 1964; 1 box (Box 446)
    - Fritz, Bernardine Szold, 1964; 1 box (Box 446)
    - Fulbright, J. William, 1964; 1 box (Box 446)
    - Gabriel, Peter P, 1964; 1 box (Box 446)
    - Gandhi, Indira, 1964; 1 box (Box 446)
    - Georgetown University, 1964; 1 box (Box 446)
    - Geraghty, James M, 1964; 1 box (Box 446)
    - Glick, Frank and Virginia, 1964; 1 box (Box 446)
    - Goheen, Robert F, 1964; 1 box (Box 446)
    - Goldman, Eric F, 1964; 1 box (Box 446)
    - Re Granges, A.B., 1964; 1 box (Box 446)
    - Greenbaum, Edward S, 1964; 1 box (Box 446)
    - Greene, Nathan, 1964; 1 box (Box 446)
    - Gulick, Luther, 1964; 1 box (Box 446)
    - Gunther, John, 1964; 1 box (Box 446)
    - Hannah, John A, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - Harper's Magazine, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - Harvard Law School, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - Harvard University, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - Heffner, Richard D, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - Herald Tribune, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - Hewlett, Richard G, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - Hoffman, Paul G, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - Hornig, Donald F, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - Hoyt, Palmer, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - Humphrey, Hubert H, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - Re India, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - Re Indus River Basin, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - Industrial Area Foundation, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - Institute for International Order, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - International Executives Association, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - International Finance Corporation, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - Iowa State University, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - Re Iran, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - Iran-America Society, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - Iran-American Chamber of Commerce, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - Iran Foundation, Inc, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - Jackson, Barbara, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - Jackson, Henry M, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - Jackson State College, Jackson, Mississippi, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - Jacobs, Mr. and Mrs. Leonard, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - Janeway, Eliot and Elizabeth, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - Jesselson, Ludwig, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - Jewish Community Center, Kansas City, Missouri, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - Julian, Percy L, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - Re Kansas University - Visit, October 12-30, 1964, 1 box (Box 447)
    - Keller, Helen, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - Kennan, George F, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - Killian, James R. Jr, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - Knight, Douglas M, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - Kraft, James, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - Lackey, Douglas W, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - Lafollette, Philip F, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - Library of Congress Manuscript Division, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - Lilienthal, Allen, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - Re Lilienthal, David E. Papers, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - Lilienthal, David E., Jr, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - Lilienthal, Michael, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - Lilienthal, Theodore, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - Lippmann, Walter, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - Lively, Robert A, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - Lleras, Alberto, 1964; 1 box (Box 447)
    - McCulloch, Frank, 1964; 1 box (Box 448)
    - McGraw-Hill Book Company, 1964; 1 box (Box 448)
    - McKelway, Benjamin M, 1964; 1 box (Box 448)
    - McMahan, Elizabeth L, 1964; 1 box (Box 448)
    - Martyn, Howe, 1964; 1 box (Box 448)
    - May, Stacy, 1964; 1 box (Box 448)
    - Mager, Albert, 1964; 1 box (Box 448)
    - Meyer, Andre, 1964; 1 box (Box 448)
    - Michigan State University, 1964; 1 box (Box 448)
    - Michigan University, Institute of Public Administration, 1964; 1 box (Box 448)
    - Minerals & Chemicals Philipp Corporation, 1964; 1 box (Box 448)
    - Minnesota University, 1964; 1 box (Box 448)
    - Miscellaneous, 1964; 1 box (Box 448)
    - Moe, Henry A, 1964; 1 box (Box 448)
    - Moore, Hugh, 1964; 1 box (Box 448)
    - Morehouse, Edward W, 1964; 1 box (Box 448)
    - Morgan, Arthur E, 1964; 1 box (Box 448)
    - Re Morgan Harcourt A, 1964; 1 box
      Includes some early correspondence, 1933 ... 1950.
      - Murphy, Franklin D, 1964; 1 box (Box 448)
    - Murrow, Edward R, 1964; 1 box (Box 448)
    - Museum of Modern Art, 1964; 1 box (Box 448)
    - Nashville Tennessean, 1964; 1 box (Box 448)
    - National Book Committee, 1964; 1 box (Box 448)
    - Re National Broadcasting Company, "Open mind" program, 1964 November 29; 1 box (Box 448)
    - Re National Conference in International Economic and Social Development, 1964; 1 box (Box 448)
    - National Council of Applied Economic Research, 1964; 1 box (Box 448)
    - National Council for Civil Responsibility, 1964; 1 box (Box 448)
    - National University Extension Association, 1964; 1 box (Box 448)
    - Near East Foundation, 1964; 1 box (Box 448)
    - Neely, Frank H, 1964; 1 box (Box 448)
    - New York State Society of Professional Engineers, 1964; 1 box (Box 448)
    - New York Times, 1964; 1 box (Box 448)
    - Re Nicely, James Mount, 1964; 1 box (Box 448)
    - Niebuhr, Reinhold, 1964; 1 box (Box 448)
    - Nizer, Louis, 1964; 1 box (Box 448)
    - North American Newspaper Alliance, 1964; 1 box (Box 448)
    - North Carolina State University, 1964; 1 box (Box 448)
    - Northwood Institute, Midland, Michigan, 1964; 1 box
      - Re Nuclear Power Plants, 1964; 1 box
        - California, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 448)
        - Connecticut, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 448)
        - New York, etc., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 448)
    - Oakes, John B, 1964; 1 box (Box 449)
    - Oliver, John, 1964; 1 box (Box 449)
    - Owen, Marguerite, 1964; 1 box (Box 449)
    - Re Pahlavi, Mohammed Reza, Shah of Iran, 1964; 1 box (Box 449)
    - Re Pakistan, 1964; 1 box (Box 449)
    - Palfrey, John G, 1964; 1 box (Box 449)
    - Peace News (London), 1964; 1 box (Box 449)
    - Perkins, James A, 1964; 1 box (Box 449)
    - University of Pittsburgh, 1964; 1 box (Box 449)
    - Planned Parenthood/World Population, 1964; 1 box (Box 449)
    - Princeton Theological Seminary, 1964; 1 box (Box 449)
    - Re Princeton University: Miscellaneous, 1964; 1 box (Box 449)
    - Re Princeton University Library, 1964; 1 box (Box 449)
    - Prud'homme, Hector, 1953-1964; 1 box
      - Re Publications, 1953-1964; 1 box
        - Big Business: A New Era, Harper & Brothers, 1953; 1 box (Box 449)
        - Change, Hope, and the Bomb, TITHAton University Press, 1963; 1 box (Box 449)
        - Journals of David E. Lilienthal, Harper & Brothers, 1964; 1 box (Box 449)
        - The Road to Change, 1964; 1 box (Box 449)
    - Radcliffe College, 1964; 1 box (Box 449)
    - Redpath Bureau, 1964; 1 box (Box 449)
    - Robertson, Robert H.S., 1964; 1 box (Box 449)
    - Robinson, Charles W, 1964; 1 box (Box 449)
    - Rockefeller, John D. ITT, 1964; 1 box (Box 449)
    - Re Rockefeller Public Service Awards, 1964; 1 box (Box 449)
    - Re Roosevelt, Eleanor - Memorial Foundation, 1964; 1 box (Box 449)
    - Rosenak, Harold, 1964; 1 box (Box 449)
    - Rosenman, Samuel I, 1964; 1 box (Box 449)
    - Rostow, Walt W, 1964; 1 box (Box 449)
    - Rusk, Dean, 1964; 1 box (Box 449)
    - Rutgers University, 1964; 1 box (Box 449)
    - St. Lawrence, Lee, 1964; 1 box (Box 450)
    - Salisbury, Harrison E, 1964; 1 box (Box 450)
    - Sandburg, Carl, 1964; 1 box (Box 450)
    - Sarnoff, David, 1964; 1 box (Box 450)
    - Schlesinger, Arthur M., Jr, 1964; 1 box (Box 450)
    - Schwartz, David, 1964; 1 box (Box 450)
    - Shelton, Barrett C, 1964; 1 box (Box 450)
    - Re Sierra Leone, 1964; 1 box (Box 450)
    - Smyth, Henry D, 1964; 1 box (Box 450)
    - Society for Advancement of Management, 1964; 1 box (Box 450)
    - Society for International Development, 1964; 1 box (Box 450)
    - Society of Nuclear Medicine, 1964; 1 box (Box 450)
    - Spock, Benjamin, 1964; 1 box (Box 450)
    - Stern, Richard S, 1964; 1 box (Box 450)
    - Stevenson, Adlai E, 1964; 1 box (Box 450)
    - Straus, Donald B, 1964; 1 box (Box 450)
    - Swidler, Joseph C, 1964; 1 box (Box 450)
    - Swing, Raymond, 1964; 1 box (Box 450)
    - Sylvester, Arthur, 1964; 1 box (Box 450)
    - Szanton, Victor L, 1964; 1 box (Box 450)
    - Re Tennessee Valley Authority, 1964; 1 box (Box 450)
    - Tobey, Mr. and Mrs. Barney, 1964; 1 box (Box 450)
    - Tobey, David M, 1964; 1 box (Box 450)
    - Tobey, Nancy, 1964; 1 box (Box 450)
    - Tour, Harry B, 1964; 1 box (Box 450)
    - Truman, Harry S, 1964; 1 box (Box 450)